(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Nyanyanyanya...
Hello everyone.
Yagoo! It's nice to dance!
Go! Go!
Oh, yes!
Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah!
Thanks.
Hi, friend!
What's that?
おい、誰やこれした？
Hey, who did this?
なんだらえ！ なんだらえ！
What is it! What is it!
こんばんは！
Good evening!
カウントナイトTVです！
This is Count Night TV!
この番組は、名誉ルーナイトであるポルナイトと...
This is a music ranking program hosted by Pornite, an honorary Lunaite...
...フブルナイトが司会でお送りする音楽ランキング番組です！
...and Fubulite!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
#姫森ルーナ生誕アニソンLIVE で拡散してね！
Spread the word with #姫森ルーナ生誕アニソンLIVE!
さてさて、本日のランキングテーマは...
Well now, today's ranking theme is...
姫森ルーナおすすめアニソン特集TOP10とのことですが...
Himemori Luna's Recommended Anime Songs Top 10 Special...
んな曲がランクインしているんでしょうね！
I wonder what songs have made the list!
それではまずは、10位から8位まで見ていきましょう！
First, let's look at 10th to 8th place!
カウントナイト！
Count Night!
10位 侵略ノススメ☆
10th: Shinryaku Nosusume☆
9位 輪舞-revolution
9th: Rinbu-revolution
8位 はじめてのチュウ
8th: Hajimete no Chuu
侵略！ 侵略！ 侵略！ 侵略！ 侵略！ 侵略！ イカ娘！
Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Squid Girl!
キラキラな海と風 輝くアトリウム
Sparkling sea and wind, a shining atrium
みんなで集まってはじめましょ はじめましょ
Let's all gather and start, let's start
ホラホラそこのキミ わがままな態度で
Hey there, you over there, with your selfish attitude
落ちたり痛くしたら イカんでしょ イカんでしょ
If you fall or get hurt, it's not good, right? It's not good.
ほんとはもっと優しい気持ちを持ってるでしょう あなたも
Actually, you have kinder feelings too, don't you?
ひとりぼっちも 海の平和も
Being lonely or the peace of the sea...
一見機嫌も 幸せも守ります！
I'll protect your mood and your happiness!
いい感じ無敵に進め
Go forward invincibly in a good way
いい感じ無邪気に進め
Go forward innocently in a good way
東の島行ったら お宝いっぱい大勝利！
If we go to the eastern island, lots of treasures, a big victory!
東の島行ったら お宝いっぱい 大勝利！
Going to the eastern island, lots of treasure, a big victory!
イーカンジ☆ムボーに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed recklessly!
イーカンジ☆ムチューに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed entrancedly!
誕生席嬉しい このまま天下を取れないイカ？
I'm happy with the birthday seat, can't I take over the world like this?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功！ 侵略 攻略 イカ娘
Invasion, capture, plan successful! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl
侵略 攻略 計画 成功！ 侵略 攻略 イカ娘 キュッ
Invasion, capture, plan successful! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl, Kyu!
侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！
Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion!
侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略！侵略 攻略 イカ娘 キュッ
Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl, Kyu!
ウキウキな海の風 駆け出すプロムナード
A cheerful sea breeze, a promenade starting to run
あなたを見つけたら 並びましょ 並びましょ
If I find you, let's line up, let's line up
ドキドキ気にしてる 始まりの５分前
My heart's pounding, five minutes before the start
オシたりおくれたりは イカンでしょ イカンでしょ
Pushing or being late is no good, right? No good, right?
ホンネはいつもかくしていたよ キズつかないようにね
I always hid my true feelings, so I wouldn't get hurt
ヒキコモリでも 平和主義でも
Even if I'm a shut-in, even if I'm a pacifist
いばらの道でも 幸せをつかみたい！
Even on a thorny path, I want to seize happiness!
イーカンジ☆ムテキに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed invincibly!
イーカンジ☆ムジャキに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed innocently!
アミとスミをかけたら 効果抜群 ハイタッチ！
If you apply the net and ink, it's super effective, high five!
イーカンジ☆ムボーに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed recklessly!
イーカンジ☆ムチューに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed entrancedly!
目指すとこが合ったら 合体仕様にならなイカ？
If our goals match, won't you join me in a combined specification?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功！ 侵略 攻略 イカ娘
Invasion, capture, plan successful! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl
侵略 攻略 計画 成功！ 侵略 攻略 イカ娘 キュッ
Invasion, capture, plan successful! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl, Kyu!
今の世の中は ちょっとキュウクツな感じ
The world today feels a bit cramped
だけど僕達は 今日も
But even today, we...
好きなものだけは 変わらないまま大人になるよ
Will grow up while keeping only the things we like unchanged
愚かなる人類！私が お前たちの腐った地上を 侵略してやるであります！
Foolish humans! I shall invade your rotten world!
イーカンジ☆ムテキに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed invincibly!
イーカンジ☆ムジャキに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed innocently!
２人でホラ いったら 想い出たくさんできました
Look, since the two of us went together, we made many memories
イーカンジ☆ムボーに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed recklessly!
イーカンジ☆ムチューに☆ススメ
It's a good feeling! Proceed entrancedly!
ひとりじゃねぇ サミシイ このまま一緒に行かなイカ？
I'm not alone, it's lonely, won't you go together with me like this?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功！ 侵略 攻略 イカ娘
Invasion, capture, plan successful! Invasion, capture, Squid Girl
侵略 攻略 侵略 攻略 侵略 攻略 イカ娘 キュッ
Invasion, capture, Invasion, capture, Invasion, capture, Squid Girl, Kyu!
輪舞 -revolution-
Rinbu -revolution-
潔く カッコ良く 生きて行こう･･･
Cleanly, coolly, let's live our lives...
たとえ２人離ればなれになっても･･･
Even if the two of us are separated...
Take my revolution
光さす庭庭 手をとり合い
In the sun-drenched garden, holding hands
誓い合った なぐさめ合った
We swore to each other, we comforted each other
もう恋は二度としないよって
Saying we'd never fall in love again
そんな強い結末は カタチ変え
Such a strong conclusion changes shape
今じゃこんなにたくましい
Now it's so robust
私達の Life style, everyday･･･ everytime
Our life style, every day... every time
頬を寄せあって
Cheek to cheek
うつる写真の笑顔に
In the smiles of the photos we take
少しの淋しさ つめ込んで
Tucking in a little bit of loneliness
潔く カッコ良く 明日からは
Cleanly, coolly, from tomorrow
誰もが振り向く女になる
I'll become a woman everyone turns to look at
たとえ２人離ればなれになっても
Even if the two of us are separated
心はずっと一緒に
Our hearts will always be together
愛はお金では買えないって
They say love can't be bought with money
知っているけど
I know, but...
愛でお金は買えるの？
Can money buy love?
T.V.で言ってた
They said so on T.V.
無感動…無関心きりがないね
Apathy... indifference, there's no end to it.
若い子みんなそうだと思われるのは
Being thought that all young people are like that...
feel so bad!
どうしようもないじゃない
There's nothing we can do about it, is there?
Oh feel so bad
でもね私達
But you know, we...
トモダチの事
...when it comes to our friends,
何より大切にしてる
...we value them more than anything else.
きっと大人よりも
Surely more than adults do.
Revolution
夢を見て 涙して 傷ついても
Even if we dream, cry, and get hurt,
現実はがむしゃらに来るし
reality comes at us recklessly.
自分の居場所 存在価値は失くせない
I can't lose my place or my worth...
自分を守るために
...in order to protect myself.
I'll go my way 戻れない それぞれの
I'll go my way, there's no turning back, for each of us,
道を選ぶ時が来る前に
...before the time comes to choose our paths.
こんなにも こんなにも
These so many, so many...
大切な想い出 とき放つよ
...precious memories, I'll set them free!
Take my revolution 生きて行こう
Take my revolution, let's live on.
現実はがむしゃらに来るし
Reality comes at us recklessly.
自分の居場所 存在価値を見つけたい
I want to find my place and my worth.
今日までの自分を
The self I've been until today...
潔く脱ぎ捨てる 裸になる
...I'll bravely cast it off and become naked.
自由を舞う薔薇のように
Like a rose dancing in freedom,
たとえ2人離ればなれになっても
...even if the two of us are separated...
私は世界を変える
...I will change the world!
はじめてのチュウ
作詞・作曲：実川 俊晴
My First Kiss
Lyrics/Composition: Toshiharu Jitsukawa
眠れない夜
A sleepless night...
君のせいだよ
...is all your fault.
さっき別れたばかりなのに
Even though we just said goodbye.
耳たぶが for you
My earlobes are for you,
燃えている for you
...burning for you.
やった やった やったよ
I did it, I did it, I really did it!
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss,
君とチュウ
...a kiss with you.
I will give you all my love
なぜか優しい気持ちが
For some reason, this kind feeling...
Ah いっぱい
...ah, is overflowing.
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss,
君とチュウ
...a kiss with you.
I will give you all my love
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
I'm tearing up, even though I'm a boy.
Be in love with you
デートコースは
The date course...
もう決めたんだ
...I've already decided on it.
明日の夢がふくらんでくる
My dreams for tomorrow are growing.
この愛を to you
This love, to you.
いつまでも to you
Forever, to you.
きっと きっと きっとさ
Surely, surely, I'm sure of it.
ohh
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss
君とチュウ
A kiss with you
I will give you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが
For some reason, a gentle feeling...
Ah いっぱい
Ah, is filling me up
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss
君とチュウ
A kiss with you
I will give you all my love.
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
Tears are coming out, even though I'm a boy
Be in love with you.
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss
君とチュウ
A kiss with you
I will give you all my love.
なぜか優しい気持ちが
For some reason, a gentle feeling...
Ah いっぱい
Ah, is filling me up
はじめてのチュウ
My first kiss
君とチュウ
A kiss with you
I will give you all my love.
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
Tears are coming out, even though I'm a boy
Be in love with you.
Lovin' you
Can't stop
ということで 3曲連続で歌っていただきました
And with that, she sang three songs in a row!
イエーイ！
Yay!
姫の歌声が沁みるのらね
The Princess's singing voice really hits home, doesn't it?
にしても 今日のステージはセットも気合入ってますな
Even so, today's stage set has a lot of effort put into it!
Count Night TV 姫のために 今年度予算を全てかけて準備いたしました
Count Night TV! For the sake of the Princess, we've prepared this with the entire year's budget!
えー！
Wait, what?!
さて お次は一気に 7位から4位まで発表です
Now, next up, let's reveal the rankings from 7th to 4th all at once!
ワクワク
*Excitement*
それでは 皆さんご一緒に
Now then, everyone together!
カウントナイト！
Count Night!
吹雪
Fubuki
デリケートに好きして
Delicate ni Suki Shite
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
だんご大家族
Dango Daikazoku
届け 届け 想いよ 届け
Reach out, reach out, let my feelings reach out
そうあの日笑顔 私の願い全て
Yes, that day's smile was all of my wishes
君と優しい時間へと
Towards a gentle time with you
届け
Reach out
海の青広がる
The blue of the sea spreads out
赤煉瓦その向こうに
Beyond those red bricks
ねえ
Hey
光る磯波越え
Crossing the sparkling waves at the shore
叢雲の空眩しい
The sky with gathering clouds is dazzling
あー
Ah
言葉選んで瞳伏せても
Even if I choose my words and cast my eyes down
見えない明日も君の笑顔も！
Neither the invisible tomorrow nor your smile!
白く白く吹雪のような
White and white, like a blizzard
そう出逢う前から解ってたこの想い
Yes, I've known these feelings since before we even met
今ならもっとずっと強く
Now, even more, much stronger
強く強く願いは強く
Strongly, strongly, my wish is strong
繋ぐよその手を感じて明日を
I'll hold on, feeling your hand, towards tomorrow
信じる優しい未来へと
Into the gentle future I believe in
届け
Reach out
水平線陽が落ちて
As the sun sets over the horizon
夕焼け君を染める
The sunset colors you
ねえ
Hey
ずっとこのままなんて
Thinking it would stay like this forever
いいじゃない想うだけなら
Is fine, if it's just a thought
けど
But
きっと違うのいかなきゃだめなの？
Surely it's different, must I go?
呼吸揃えたら飛沫の中へ！
If we synchronize our breathing, into the spray!
君と　君と　唄っていたい
I want to sing with you, with you
戦の日それはきっと全てでなくて
The day of battle is surely not everything
帰り道見失わぬよう
So we don't lose our way back
聴いて　聴いて　その声聴いて
Listen, listen, listen to that voice
繋いでこの手を　還るよ明日に
Hold this hand, we'll return to tomorrow
きっと懐かしいあの場所へ
Surely to that nostalgic place
時の嵐の中で今
Now, in the storm of time
舞い散る花の涙
Falling petals of flower tears
向かい風　今宵　花吹雪
A headwind, tonight a cherry blossom blizzard
積もる　積もる　白雪みたいに
Piling up, piling up, like white snow
優しく透きとおる時間のような
Like a gently transparent time
きっと　きっと　初雪みたいに
Surely, surely, like the first snow
忘れないよ一瞬を―
I won't forget this moment—
深く　深く　深雪のような
Deep, deep, like deep snow
そう始まる前に知っていたこの痛み
Yes, this pain I knew before it started
今ならもっとずっと深く
Now, even much deeper
強く　強く　想い紡いで
Strongly, strongly, spinning my thoughts
繋ぐよその手を　感じて明日を
I'll hold that hand, feeling tomorrow
静かな優しい海へきっと届け
Surely reach that quiet, gentle sea
届け
Reach
君へと届け
Reach to you
泡へと届け
Reach to the sea foam
デリケートに好きして
Love Me Delicately
作詞・作曲：古田 喜昭
Lyrics/Composition: Yoshiaki Furuta
男の子とちがう　女の子って
Girls are different from boys
好きと嫌いだけで　普通がないの
With only 'like' and 'dislike', there's no 'normal'
でも好きになったら　いくつかの
But when I fall in love, I'll show you
魔法を見せるわ　本当よ
Some magic, really
そうよ　女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart is
星空に　月の小舟浮かべ
Setting a moon-shaped boat afloat in the starry sky
夢を探すこともできる
Even searching for dreams is possible
デリケートに好きして　デリケートに　好きして　好きして　好きして
Love me delicately, delicately, love me, love me, love me
嫌いと感じたら　手遅れみたい
If I feel like I dislike it, it seems too late
サヨナラが心に　あふれてしまう
Goodbyes start overflowing in my heart
興味ない人と　一秒も
I can't stay for even a second
一緒にいられない　私達
With someone I'm not interested in, we can't
そうよ　女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart is
七色に　光る虹のように
Like a rainbow shining in seven colors
風が吹くだけでも　変わる
Changing with even just a breath of wind
デリケートに好きして　デリケートに　好きして　好きして　好きして
Love me delicately, delicately, love me, love me, love me
そうよ　女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart is
星空に　月の小舟浮かべ
Setting a moon-shaped boat afloat in the starry sky
夢を探すこともできる
Even searching for dreams is possible
デリケートに好きして
Please love me delicately
好きして 好きして 好きして
Love me, love me, love me
アニソン特集 TOP10
Anime Song Special TOP 10
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
我愛你 酔いが醒めない
Wo ai ni, I can't sober up
我愛你 恋が醒めない
Wo ai ni, this love won't wake up
お生憎様の慣れ果てで
In the ruins of a sorry state
察して
Guess it
無問題 破滅してみて
No problem, try to be destroyed
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対 お手お座りで
Strong opposition, give paw and sit
ハイ報酬
High reward
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is pricking
僕はドクンドクン
I am thumping
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is pricking
僕はドクンドクン
I am thumping
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Try erasing loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も独裁して
Dictate both love and romance
僕を独占して
Monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよ
Let's keep kissing until we become addicted
そして Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
And Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
熱く とろけるくらいに 溢れた気持ちが たまらないでしょ
Hot and melting, these overflowing feelings are unbearable, right?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get on! 我愛你 無問題
Get on! Wo ai ni, no problem
Get Get Get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pon, chi, kan, the match is always
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Absurd, if you ask me
ちんぷんかんぷんだ 最後はロンでしょ？
It's all gibberish, in the end it's Ron, right?
もう何回？ 殺られればいい
How many more times? It's fine to be killed
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, I can't forget
終わんないで トキメキ 偏愛 予習
Don't end, heartbeat, partiality, preparation
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is pricking
僕はドクンドクン
I am thumping
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is pricking
僕はドクンドクン
I am thumping
心臓ごと引きずり出してみてよ
Try to drag it out with my heart
きもちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, though it's a hassle
やっぱ照れくさいけど
I'm still embarrassed after all
死ぬまで 忘れられない チューしよ
Let's kiss so I can't forget until I die
いかれた街は ゾンビで溢れる
The crazy city is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me
ときめく胸に 繋がるロープを 引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to your throbbing chest
いくよ Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Here I go! Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
本気で 狂えるくらいの 虚しさが 美しいでしょ
The emptiness that makes you go mad is beautiful, right?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
せーの ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Ready? Pon, chi, kan, it won't end
Get Get Get on chu!
ほらね 我愛你 無問題
See? Wo ai ni, no problem
Get Get Get on chu!
だんご大家族
Dango Daikazoku
だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご 大家族
Dango, dango, dango, dango, dango, dango, big family
やんちゃな焼きだんご やさしいあんだんご
Mischievous grilled dango, gentle bean paste dango
すこし夢見がちな 月見だんご
A slightly dreamy moon-viewing dango
おすましごまだんご 四つ子串だんご
Dignified sesame dango, quadruplet skewered dango
みんなみんなあわせて 100人家族
Everyone together, a family of 100
赤ちゃんだんごは いつも幸せの中で
The baby dango is always in happiness
年寄りだんごは 目を細めてる
The elderly dango are smiling gently
なかよしだんご 手をつなぎ 大きなまるい輪になるよ
Hand in hand, the friendly dango form a big, round circle.
町をつくり だんご星の上 みんなで笑いあおうよ
Let's build a town on the dango planet and all laugh together.
うさぎも空で手をふってみてる でっかいおつきさま
The rabbit in the sky is waving too, from the giant moon.
うれしいこと 悲しいことも 全部まるめて
Taking all the happy things and all the sad things, and rolling them all up together.
みんな、今日は見に来てくれてありがとのなの。
Everyone, thank you for coming to see me today.
いつもルーナイトに『家族』ってこと？ってコメントされて、
I'm always getting comments from Luna-Knights asking, "So we're family?"
『違うのな』って否定してきたけど、
And I've always denied it, saying, "No, you're not."
今だけは、んなたんとルーナイトは家族ってことにしてあげるのなら！
But just for now, I'll let you Luna-Knights be my family!
ルーナイト、大好きなのならよ！
I love you Luna-Knights!
なかよしだんご 手をつなぎ 大きなまるい輪になるよ
Hand in hand, the friendly dango form a big, round circle.
町をつくり だんご星の上 みんなで笑いあおうよ
Let's build a town on the dango planet and all laugh together.
うさぎも空で手をふってみてる でっかいおつきさま
The rabbit in the sky is waving too, from the giant moon.
うれしいこと 悲しいことも 全部まるめて
Taking all the happy things and all the sad things, and rolling them all up together.
ラララ...
La la la...
だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご 大家族
Dango dango dango dango dango dango family
さて、ランキングものこすところ3位から1位となりましたね！
Well, only the 3rd to 1st place rankings are left!
何が1位になるんでしょうか！
I wonder what will be number one!
と、その前に、スペシャルステージを挟ませてもらうわよ！
But before that, let's have a special stage!
え、なになにそれ？
Wait, what's that?
こちらをご覧ください！
Please take a look at this!
ひとりごつ
Hitorigotsu (Soliloquy)
なんだ... もう朝か... と...
What... Is it morning already...
ひとり... ごつ...
Just... a soliloquy...
焼けたパンにバタ ぬり... ぬり...
Spreading... spreading butter on toasted bread...
やんだ... 雨はなんか... しめって...
The rain has stopped... It feels kind of damp...
なま... がわ... き...
Damp... and... dry...
へんな... あし... あと... だと思っ... たらぁ
I thought... it was a strange... footprint...
きのう晩につけた あし... あと...
The footprint I made last night...
やけに... 土が... 水をふくんで
The soil is so full of water.
なま... がわき...
Damp and dry...
あぁ～～～っ きんと冷え～～～てるぅ
Ahh... It's freezing cold.
缶カンがぁ あぁ～ なんか冷たくて
The can is, ahh, somehow cold.
あぁ～ 汗と結露が混じって
Ahh, sweat and condensation are mixing.
あぁ～ 靴をぬらしてるぅ
Ahh, it's wetting my shoes.
しめっ... てる...
It's... damp...
なま... がわ... き...
Damp... and... dry...
ポルナイト、感極まりすぎて泣いちゃった。
Pol-Night, I got so emotional and cried.
気を取り直して。さあ、スペシャルステージで盛り上がったところで、3位から1位の発表だ！
Let's get back on track. Now that we've had a blast on the special stage, it's time to announce 3rd to 1st place!
せーの！
One, two...
カウントナイト！
Count Night!
3位 恋のミクル伝説
3rd: The Legend of Mikuru's Love
2位 Get Wild
2nd: Get Wild
1位 ドラゴンボールメドレー
1st: Dragon Ball Medley
ミ・ミ・ミラクル ミクルンルン☆
Mi-Mi-Miracle Mikurunrun☆
素直に「好き」と言えないキミも
Even you, who can't honestly say "I love you"
勇気を出して(Hey, Attack!!)
Must summon your courage (Hey, Attack!!)
恋のまじない ミクルビーム
A love incantation, Mikuru Beam
かけてあげるわ
I'll cast it on you
未来からやってきたおしゃまなキューピッド
A precocious Cupid who came from the future
いつもみんなの夢を運ぶの
Always carrying everyone's dreams
夜はひとり星たちに願いをかける
At night, I make a wish to the stars all alone
明日もあの人に会えますように
I hope I can meet that person again tomorrow
Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
涙をふいて走り出したら
Once you've wiped your tears and started running
Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
宙の彼方へ Special Generation
Towards the far reaches of space, Special Generation
「いつになったら、大人になれるのかなぁ？」
"I wonder when I'll be able to become an adult?"
ミ・ミ・ミラクル ミクルンルン☆
Mi-Mi-Miracle Mikurunrun☆
出世の遅いアナタのパパも
Even your father, who's slow to get promoted
元気を出して「飲みにいこう！」
Must cheer up, "Let's go for a drink!"
ふしぎなパワー ミクルビーム
A mysterious power, Mikuru Beam
かけてあげるわ
I'll cast it on you
未来にもあるのかな勇気と希望
I wonder if courage and hope exist in the future too
もしもなかったら少し困るな
It'd be a bit of a problem if they didn't
あの人もいつの日か私を捨てる
One day, even that person will abandon me
そんなのイヤよ、強く抱いてね
I don't want that, hold me tight
Come On! Get chance! Baby!
TOBで株を買い占め
Buy up all the shares with a TOB
Come On! Get chance! Baby!
三年越しに Monkey Magic Tonight
Three years later, Monkey Magic Tonight
Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
涙をふいて走り出したら
Once you've wiped your tears and started running
Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
宙の彼方へ Special Generation
Towards the far reaches of space, Special Generation
「キスって、どんな味がするんだろ…」
"I wonder what a kiss tastes like..."
恋のマジカル ミクルンルン☆ (Ah)
Love's magical Mikurunrun☆ (Ah)
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Tearing through the asphalt tires
暗闇走りぬける
Running through the darkness
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I give myself over to cheap thrills
明日におびえていたよ
I was afraid of tomorrow
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for the sake of someone...
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何もこわくはない
I'm not afraid of anything
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding a puzzle of love that can't be solved alone
Get wild and tough
この街で やさしさに甘えていたくはない
In this city, I don't want to rely on kindness
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものがどこかにあるさ
Somewhere, there's something only you can protect
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりもどすよ
Even alone, I'll regain my wounded dreams
クルマのライトにKissを投げては
Blowing kisses to the car lights
車道で踊るあの娘
That girl dances on the roadway
冷たい夜空をステージにして
Making the cold night sky her stage
哀しくおどけていたね
She was jokingly sad, wasn't she?
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために愛せるのなら
If I can love for the sake of someone...
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
きっと 強くなれる
I'm sure I can become stronger
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 消せない痛み心に抱いて
Holding a pain in my heart that can't be erased alone
Get wild and tough
この街で 自由をもてあましたくはない
In this city, I don't want to have too much freedom
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものをみつけだしたら
Once you find the thing that only you can protect
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりもどすよ
Even alone, I'll regain my wounded dreams
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding a puzzle of love that can't be solved alone
Get wild and tough
この街で やさしさに甘えていたくはない
In this city, I don't want to rely on kindness
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものがどこかにあるさ
Somewhere, there's something only you can protect
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりもどすよ
Even alone, I'll regain my wounded dreams
Get wild and tough...
魔訶不思議アドベンチャー！
Mystical Adventure!
つかもうぜ！ DRAGON BALL
Let's catch them! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー スリルな秘密
The world's number one thrilling secret
さがそうぜ！ DRAGON BALL
Let's search for them! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー ユカイな奇跡
The world's number one happy miracle
この世はでっかい宝島
This world is a giant treasure island
そうさ今こそ アドベンチャー！
That's right, now is the time for adventure!
胸ワクワクの愛が GISSRI
My heart is PACKED with exciting love
色とりどりの夢が DOSSARI
There are HEAPS of colorful dreams
この世のどこかで ひかってる
Shining somewhere in this world
そいつを見つけに ゆこうぜ BOY
Let's go find them, boy!
妖怪変化も ぶっとばし
Blowing away the shapeshifting monsters
雲のマシンで 今日も飛ぶのさ
Flying today too on a cloud machine
Let's try try try 魔訶不思議
Let's try try try, mystical
空を駆け抜け 山を越え
Racing through the sky, over the mountains
Let's fly fly fly 大冒険
Let's fly fly fly, a great adventure
不思議な旅が 始まるぜ
A mysterious journey is beginning
手にいれろ！ DRAGON BALL
Get them in your hands! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー てごわいチャンス
The world's number one tough chance
追いかけろ！ DRAGON BALL
Chase after them! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー イカした物語
The world's number one cool story
この世はでっかい宝島
This world is a giant treasure island
そうさ今こそアドベンチャー！
That's right, now's the time for adventure!
光る 雲を突き抜け Fly Away
Flying through the shining clouds, Fly Away
からだじゅうに 広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreading through my whole body
顔を 蹴られた地球が怒って
The earth, kicked in the face, gets angry
火山を爆発させる
And makes a volcano explode
溶けた 北極の中に
Inside the melted North Pole
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
If there were dinosaurs, I'd want to train them to balance on balls
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へのへのカッパ
Whatever happens, it's no big deal
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉
A Spirit Bomb so loud it makes my heart throb
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭カラッポの方が 夢詰め込める
An empty head is better for stuffing in dreams
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラZで 今日もアイアイアイアイ……
With an Ultra Z smile, today too, ai-ai-ai-ai...
Sparking!
ハチャメチャが 押し寄せて来る
Chaos comes rushing in
泣いてる 場合じゃない
It's no time for crying
ワクワクを 100倍にして
Make the excitement 100 times greater
パーティーの 主役になろう
And become the star of the party
夢中になれる モノが
The things that can make you obsessed
いつか君を すげぇ奴にするんだ
Will one day make you an awesome guy
NO-TEN P-KAN 空は晴れて
Brain clear, the sky is sunny
IPPAI OPPAI ボク元気
Full of chest, I'm energetic
トラブルと遊べ ヤンチャ・ボーイ
Play with trouble, naughty boy
We gotta power! ドラゴンボールZ
We gotta power! Dragon Ball Z
NO-TEN P-KAN 頭さえて
Brain clear, mind sharp
RA-MEN ROPPAI ハハのん気
Six bowls of ramen, haha, easygoing
世紀末はしゃげ オチャメ・ガール
Frolic at the end of the century, mischievous girl
We gotta power! ドラゴンボールZ
We gotta power! Dragon Ball Z
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
Bit by bit, you're charming my heart
その眩しい 笑顔に
With that dazzling smile
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう Hold my hand
Let's fly out from the endless darkness, Hold my hand
君と出合ったとき
When I met you
子どものころ大切に想っていた景色を思い出したんだ
I remembered the scenery I held dear as a child
僕と踊ってくれないか
Won't you dance with me?
光と影の Winding Road
The Winding Road of light and shadow
今でも あいつに夢中なの？
Are you still obsessed with him?
少しだけ 振り向きたくなるような時もあるけど
Sometimes I feel like looking back just a little
愛と勇気と誇りを持って闘うよ
But I'll fight with love, courage, and pride
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
DAN DAN my heart is being drawn in
この宇宙の希望のかけら
A fragment of hope in this universe
きっと誰もが 永遠を手に入れたい
Surely everyone wants to obtain eternity
ZEN ZEN 気にしないフリしても
Even if I pretend not to care at all
ほら君に恋してる
Look, I'm in love with you
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう Hold your hand
Let's fly out from the endless darkness, Hold your hand
ということで、ランキングトップテンまで聞いてくれてありがとうなならよ〜
So, thank you for listening until the top 10 of the ranking!
みんな、これで終わりと思った？
Everyone, did you think this was the end?
実は、ラストに重大なお知らせがあるななら〜！
Actually, there's a major announcement at the end!
ふふっ、なんだと思う？
Hehe, what do you think it is?
とその前に、グッズCMへゴー！
But before that, let's go to the merch CM!
ほーい！今年もきたぞ、誕生日記念グッズ〜
Hoi! It's here again this year, the birthday celebration merch!
詳細を見てくななら
Please take a look at the details.
まずはこちら。ルーナのおっぺぇマウスパッド2nd♡
First is this: Luna's Oppai Mousepad 2nd♡
満を持して、第2弾が登場ななら！
The second version is finally here!
イラストはかんざきパッパ描き下ろし
The illustration is newly drawn by Kanzaki-pappa.
セクシーなんなたんがみんなのお疲れの手を癒やしてくれるなら
Sexy Luna-tan will heal your tired hands.
次はこちら。お疲れ様ななのらにトートバッグ♡
Next is this: 'Good work, nanora' tote bag♡
キーホルダーのチェーンを付けられるタイプのトートバッグになってるのら
It's a tote bag that you can attach a keychain to.
デザインも可愛いなならでしょう？
The design is cute too, right?
みんな、いっぱい使ってね
Everyone, please use it a lot.
次はこちら。一緒にお出かけミニぬいぐるみキーホルダー♡
Next is this: 'Going out together' mini plush keychain♡
なんなたんがルーナイトを抱っこしているデザインになってるのら
It's a design where Luna-tan is hugging a LuKnight.
これでいつも一緒なならね
Now we can always be together.
次はこちら。ルーナとルーナイトのキラキラピンバッジ♡
Next is this: Luna and LuKnight's sparkly pin badge♡
ラメやストーンなどが施された、豪華仕様のピンバッジセットなのら
It's a luxurious pin badge set with glitter and stones.
トートバッグに付けてね
Please attach it to your tote bag.
次はこちら。ボイス
Next is this: Voices.
なんなたんはボイスはあまり出さないのだけど、今回は特別に出しちゃうのら！
I don't release voices very often, but this time I'm releasing them specially!
1つ目は、なんなたんとイチャイチャ♡デートボイス
The first one is: Flirting with Luna-tan♡ Date Voice.
そして2つ目は、添い寝なっしょいASMRボイス♡
And the second one is: Sleeping together ASMR Voice♡
特別ボイスなので、じっくり聞いてなならね
They are special voices, so please listen to them carefully.
そして、フルセット購入特典もあるのら！
And there are also full set purchase bonuses!
数量限定版は、直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージ入りななら！
The limited quantity version includes a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicate message!
今回から数量限定なので、ぜひゲットしてなならね
It's limited quantity starting from this time, so please be sure to get it.
改めてフルセットはこちらとなります
Once again, here is the full set.
そして！フルセット特典として、今年の9月から発売されるホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚つくのら！
And! As a bonus, you'll get one card for the Hololive Official Card Game, which will be released this September!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となるのらよ
The card is only for those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
グッズはこの後オープンです、みんなよろしくなならね
Merch sales will open after this. Please support me, everyone.
グッズのCMは以上でした、スタジオにお戻ししま〜す
That's it for the merch CM. Back to the studio~
はい！ということで、グッズよろしくなならよ〜
Yes! So, please support the merch~
そして重大発表！とうとう発表するなならね
And now, the major announcement! I'm finally announcing it.
なんと！オリジナルソング第4弾！
Believe it or not! My 4th original song!
タイトルは、『守ってルーナイト』を歌うのら！
The title is 'Mamotte Lunaight', and I'm going to sing it!
この生誕配信後にMVの公開と、24時に楽曲もリリースされるのら！
The MV will be released after this stream, and the song will be out at midnight!
それでは聴いてください。守ってルーナイト
Now, please listen. 'Mamotte Lunaight'.
跪きなさい
Kneel before me.
汝、この城の扉を叩いた者よ
You, who have knocked on the gates of this castle.
誓いなさい
Take an oath.
このルーナの盾となり矛となり
Become Luna's shield and spear.
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until you can sleep soundly at night.
ともにあることを！
Be with me!
捧げなさい！
Offer it up!
姫であるぞ！
I am the Princess!
ルーナって？
Luna is...?
「紅茶のカップかちゃかちゃ鳴らさないってえらい！」
"You're so good for not clinking your teacup!"
「スコーンだってこぼさず綺麗に食べてすごい！」
"You're amazing for eating your scones without making crumbs!"
「たまーに王冠どっちが前か間違っちゃうのかわいい！」
"It's so cute when you occasionally forget which way your crown goes!"
通ってよしなのら… 開城〜！
You may pass... Open the gates!
ルーナイト第一条！誰よりルーナが好きな人！
Luna Knight Rule #1! Someone who loves Luna more than anyone!
ルーナイト第二条！シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Luna Knight Rule #2! Bring me a silk duvet!
ルーナイト第三条！三時のお茶会来れる人！
Luna Knight Rule #3! Someone who can come to the 3 PM tea party!
守れなかったら即・制裁！
Immediate punishment if you can't keep them!
分かってほしいのら……
I want you to understand...
これも、帝王学を学ぶため……
This is also for the sake of learning monarchical studies...
愛という名の……教育なのら〜！
It's... education in the name of love!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
想ってくんないと
If you don't think of me
プロムナード ボイコットなのなのら！
I'll boycott the promenade!
手の甲に忠誠 誓えるの？ Chu
Can you swear loyalty on the back of my hand? Mwah
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
かまってくんないと
If you don't pay attention to me
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies and candies I have
君がいなきゃやだって！
It's no good if you're not here!
みんな心して
Everyone, prepare your hearts
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
And offer them up! For I am the Princess!
ルーナって？
Luna is...?
「お菓子のあと ちゃんと歯磨きするの えらい！」
"You're so good for brushing your teeth after sweets!"
「目覚ましなくたって 起きられちゃうの すごい！」
"You're amazing for waking up without an alarm!"
「ステップこんがらがっちゃったのも かわいい！」
"It's also cute when your steps get all tangled up!"
今日の誉め言葉、よしなのら… 開城〜！
Today's praise words are good... Open the gates!
ルーナイト第四条！ルーナを本気にさせる人！
Luna Knight Rule #4! Someone who makes Luna get serious!
ルーナイト第五条！ダイヤの花とか摘んできて！
Luna Knight Rule #5! Pick some diamond flowers for me!
ルーナイト第六条！ドラゴンヘッドに出来る人！
Luna Knight Rule #6! Someone who can do a dragon head!
つべこべ言わずに即・実行！
Don't complain, just do it immediately!
きっと分かってくれるのら……
I'm sure you'll understand...
君主論だって読んだのら……
I even read "The Prince"...
恋はいつだって……試練なのら〜！
Love is always... a trial!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
想ってくんないと
If you don't think of me
オペラハウス 貸し切りなのなのら！
I'll rent out the whole opera house!
貫いて忠誠 約束の Chu
Follow through on your loyalty, a promise mwah
ドレスの薔薇 咲かせてロンド！
Make the roses on my dress bloom, Rondo!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
わかってくんないと
If you don't understand me
バルコニー レモンティー 月にシュガー乗せちゃう
I'll put sugar on the moon from my balcony with lemon tea
あの子も綺麗だって そんなたわごとは…
Saying that other girl is pretty too, such nonsense...
おやめなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
Stop it! For I am the Princess!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
想ってくんないと
If you don't think of me
プロムナード ボイコットなのなのら！
I'll boycott the promenade!
永遠の忠誠 この指に Chu
Eternal loyalty, a mwah on this finger
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put on my glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナナイト
Protect me, Luna Knight
かまってくんないと
If you don't pay attention to me
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies and candies I have
君がいなきゃやだって！
It's no good if you're not here!
みんな心して
Everyone, prepare your hearts
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
And offer them up! For I am the Princess!
出演：姫森ルーナ
ルーナイト
Cast: Himemori Luna
Luna Knights
司会：白上フブキ、尾丸ポルカ
MC: Shirakami Fubuki, Houmaru Polka
撮影・企画補佐：カバー株式会社
Filming/Planning Support: COVER Corp.
イラストレーター：Noyu
ロゴクリエイター：柊椋
Illustrator: Noyu
Logo Creator: Hiira
振付制作：まいどん（おでんガールズ）
Choreography: Maidon (Oden Girls)
映像制作：kanauru
Video Production: kanauru
企画：姫森ルーナ
Project Planning: Himemori Luna
総合演出：姫森ルーナ
Overall Direction: Himemori Luna
協力：ルーナイト達、カバー株式会社
Cooperation: Luna Knights, COVER Corp.
監督：姫森ルーナ
Director: Himemori Luna
このあとは MV公開！
MV reveal coming up next!